vectorcast.com 2019-01-22

# Privacy Policy | Vector Software

Vector Software, Inc. (collectively, "we", "our", "us" or "Vector Software") is committed to your privacy. This privacy policy describes how Vector Software collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website [www.vectorcast.com](http://www.vectorcast.com/) (each a "Website" and collectively, "Websites"). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. We encourage you to read this privacy policy carefully when using our Website, or when providing information to us through our Website. You understand that by using our Website you are accepting our practices as described in this privacy statement.

_**What Information Do We Collect and Why?**_

IP Address  
We may use your IP address (not your e-mail address) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website, or to gather broad demographic information.

Cookies  
We use cookies to enhance the user experience and deliver personalized content. Cookies help us to deliver information specific to your interests and to save your having to re-enter your password each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow us to better analyze our site traffic patterns so that we can improve our Website offering.

User Registration  
You may choose to fill out a registration form on our Website with contact information that we, or our business partners may need. This information is used to send you requested information or products, to contact you with other product information, news or promotions, and to learn more about our Website visitors.

E-Mail Addresses  
If you give us your e-mail address, we will communicate with you via e-mail. However, we do not share your e-mail address with others outside our company. You can choose not to receive e-mails at any time.

Online Surveys  
From time to time, we may conduct online surveys. Our surveys may ask you for demographic information, such as ZIP code or your industry sector. If the online survey collects contact data, we may use that data to send you additional information only if we specifically asked for your permission in the survey. You are free to opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time.

Social Media (Features) and Widgets  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Share button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Links to Other Sites  
This site contains links to other sites. Vector Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Websites. Please refer to the policies of the respective sites.

**How We Use Visitor Information**

The information we gather through Google Analytics and Act-On software is for the sole purpose of refining the content on our site and providing you with the information you requested. We use analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a users’ prior visits to our Website. Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363) at the corresponding links.

This Website uses Act-On forms to give visitors the opportunity to request services or more information about our product offerings. You may request to be deleted from the Act-On database at any time.                                                            

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
We reserve the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason, without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy on this Website. You should check our Website frequently to see the current Privacy Policy that is in effect and any changes that may have been made to it. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or policies regarding our privacy practices that govern the use of this Website.

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us in writing or email using the information below.

Vector Software, Inc.  
1351 South County Trail, Suite 310  
East Greenwich, RI 02818
